[ Man ] YOU ACTUALLY LIED FOR ME .
[ Woman ] I LIED FOR ME .
OH , NO , NO , NO , COME ON . YOU--YOU LIED FOR BOTH OF US .
YOU ACTUALLY DID SOMETHING DECENT FOR ME .
THAT 'S A PART OF HISTORY YOU CAN 'T CHANGE .
THAT WAS A STOP SIGN .
YOU 'RE KIDDING , RIGHT ?
IN YOUR CAR , I 'D BE KIDDING ?
ON THIS ROAD ?
I HAVEN 'T SEEN A CAR IN 50 MILES .
[ Engine revving ]
COME ON , DARRY .
YAY , " GAY FEVER " !
NO , " GAY FOREVER . "
" GAY FOREVER . "
HA ! THAT 'S MINE .
THAT 'S 3 FOR LITTLE BRO ' .
THAT 'S A 6 , NOT A G , YOU IDIOT .
THAT 'S " SEXY FOREVER . " THAT 'S MINE .
THAT 'S 5 TO 2 .
SHIT .
" GAY FEVER ? "
[ Darry ] OH !
SEXY FOREVER , HUH ?
YOU KNOW THAT IS YOU IN 40 YEARS .
YEAH .
YOU KNOW , THERE 'S USUALLY A REASON WHEN YOU LIKE THE LONG WAY HOME .
GEE , LIKE ...
MAYBE I LIKE THE COUNTRY ?
OK .
JUST DRIVE , BRAT .
HEY , I 'M ONLY THINKING THE SAME THING MOM AND DAD ARE GONNA BE THINKING .
" TRISHA ?
" TRISHA , WHY ARE YOU DRIVING HOME
" FOR SPRING BREAK WITH YOUR BRAT BROTHER
" AND NOT HEADING OFF SOMEWHERE
" WITH THAT NICE 'MR . POLI-SCI-TRACK-TEAM GUY ' ? "
I WILL TELL THEM THE EXACT SAME THING I 'LL TELL YOU
NONE OF YOUR GODDAMN BUSINESS .
WHAT ? WHAT , YOU DON 'T THINK I COULD UNDERSTAND
THE COMPLEX NATURE OF YOUR RELATIONSHIPS ?
NO , I LOOK AT YOU AS A REAL EXPERT .
HUH , WHATEVER . I DON 'T- -
I DON 'T CARE .
I 'M JUST SAYING , IF YOU BROKE IT OFF WITH HIM ,
YOU SHOULD AT LEAST FIGURE OUT
WHAT YOU 'RE GONNA TELL MOM AND DAD .
THEY 'RE THE ONES IN LOVE WITH THE GUY .
[ Preacher ] WHAT WOULD JESUS DO ...
[ Woman ] ... ALFALFA GRASS SEASON ...
[ Woman ] I AM NO FANATIC . WHAT I AM IS A FAN OF GOD !
[ Preacher ] ... A SERPENT-HEADED DEMON , SHAKING YOU BY THE ...
[ Turns radio off ]
YOU WANTED THE BACK WAY HOME .
THAT 'S 10 HOURS OF PREACHERS , FARM REPORTS , AND COUNTRY .
COULD YOU POSSIBLY JUST SHUT UP AND DRIVE , PLEASE ?
¶ YOU BROKE MY HEART IN 2 ¶
¶ NOW I CAN 'T FIND THE DUCT TAPE ¶
¶ TO PUT IT TOGETHER FOR YOU ¶
COME ON , GIRL , SING ALONG NOW .
¶ WHEN I MET YOU , I THOUGHT I WOULD DIE ¶
¶ I WANTED TO CRY
¶ DIDN 'T KNOW YOU WERE EVIL ¶
¶ OR THAT YOU WOULD HURT ME ¶
¶ MR. POLI-SCI - TRACK-TEAM GUY ¶
¶ TURNS OUT YOU 'RE A TWIT AND A REAL- - ¶
[ Truck horn blowing ]
JESUS !
WHAT THE HELL 'S HIS PROBLEM ?
JUST GET OUT OF HIS WAY , DARRY !
[ Truck horn blowing ]
LET HIM PASS YOU , DARRY ! WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING ?
GO AROUND ME !
[ Trish ] GET OFF THE ROAD AND LET HIM PASS YOU !
HE 'S NUTS !
I KNOW HE 'S NUTS . PULL OVER !
GO AROUND ME !
SLOW DOWN AND LET HIM FUCKING PASS YOU !
I 'M TRYING !
[ Trish ] JESUS !
SHIT !
WHAT THE HELL WAS HIS PROBLEM ?
MY FIRST GUESS ?
INBREEDING !
GET A LOAD OF THAT NASTY OLD THING .
WHAT IS THAT ,
THE VEHICLE OF CHOICE FOR ASSHOLES AND ...
FUCKING SERIAL KILLERS ?
GOD .
YOU KNOW WHAT I JUST THOUGHT OF , RIGHT ?
KENNY AND DARLA ?
TRISH , THEY DIED ABOUT 100 MILES FROM HERE .
IT 'S THE SAME HIGHWAY .
THIS HIGHWAY RUNS THE LENGTH OF THE STATE .
YOU BELIEVE IT ?
THAT THEY HAD TO GO LOOKING FOR HER HEAD ?
THAT THEY NEVER FOUND THEM , ONLY THE CAR .
NO , NO , NO , THEY NEVER FOUND HER HEAD .
THEY FOUND THE CAR .
THEY DIDN 'T FIND HIM OR HER HEAD .
GOD , LOOK AT ME , I 'M STILL SHAKING !
YOU DON 'T THINK EVERY GENERATION HAS THEIR CAUTIONARY TALE
OF DRINKING AND DRIVING ON PROM NIGHT ?
NO , NO . I ALWAYS HEARD IT WAS TRUE .
WHEATON VALLEY HIGH , CLASS OF ' 78 .
YOU WANNA KNOW SOMETHING ?
HMM .
WHEN I FIRST HEARD THAT STORY ...
I USED TO THINK THIS WAS THE HIGHWAY I WOULD DIE ON .
QUITE THE CHEERY THINKER TODAY , AREN 'T WE , SIS ?
GOD !
WHAT 'S " POLI-SCI GUY " BEEN DOING TO YOU , ANYWAY ?
" BEATING YOU ? "
THAT WAS THE LICENSE PLATE ON THE VAN WE JUST SAW .
B-E-A-T-N-G-U .
SO ...
" BEATING YOU . "
THAT 'S MINE .
THAT 'S 3 TO 5 . OH , SHIT !
YOU CAN 'T CALL IT NOW .
MY ASS !
YOU HAVE TO CALL IT WHEN YOU SEE IT .
I WAS IN SHOCK !
TOUGH !
WHAT IS THIS , A BRAND NEW RULE , HUH ?
IT 'S ALWAYS BEEN THIS WAY .
SINCE WHEN ?
[ Trish ] SINCE ALWAYS .
SINCE JUST NOW , MAYBE .
YOUR MEMORY 'S FOR SHIT .
NO , IT 'S NOT .
UH-HUH .
NAH-UH .
UH-HUH . NAH-UH .
UH-UH . NAH-UH .
[ Both ] NAH-UH , NAH-UH , NAH-UH ...
UH-HUH , UH-HUH , UH-HUH ...
NAH-UH , INFINITY .
NAH- -
UH-HUH , INFINITY SQUARED .
[ Darry ] OKAY , NAME IT .
[ Trish ] WHAT ?
WHEN WE MADE THE RULE THAT YOU HAD TO CALL IT AS SOON AS YOU SEE IT .
WOULD YOU GIVE IT UP ALREADY ?
NO . THAT 'S ' CAUSE ...
THE RULE 'S ALWAYS BEEN
THE FIRST PERSON WHO CALLS IT , GETS IT .
YOU TALK TO MOM LATELY ?
TO TELL HER I 'D BE HOME FOR BREAK .
SHE SOUND WEIRD ?
WHAT ?
DID YOU LISTEN TO HER VOICE ?
COULD YOU SPECIFY , PLEASE ?
FORGET IT .
DID YOU DRINK THE LAST WATER ?
THE LAST ONE WAS MINE .
DAMMIT .
OH , YOU ARE A CLASS ACT , YOU KNOW THAT ?
HEY , YOU LIVE OFF-CAMPUS .
YOU EVER TRY AND DO LAUNDRY IN A DORM ?
WHAT THEY DON 'T STEAL , THEY DYE PINK .
I 'VE GOT , LIKE , 12 PAIRS OF ROSY-PINK JOCKEY SHORTS .
WELL , MAYBE THEY KNOW SOMETHING ABOUT YOU ... THAT YOU DON 'T .
" HI , MOM . HAVEN 'T SEEN YOU IN FOREVER .
" HERE 'S MY DIRTY SHORTS . " NICE .
IT 'S FOR HER , NOT ME .
WHAT ?
I HAVE TO BRING HOME LAUNDRY .
IF I DON 'T , SHE GETS DEPRESSED .
SHE THINKS I DON 'T NEED HER ANYMORE OR SOMETHING .
I 'M SERIOUS .
GOOF .
BITCH .
MAMA 'S BOY .
DADDY 'S WHORE .
DICK LICKER .
BALL SNIFFER .
ASS KISSER .
BUTT PICKER .
AH-HA-HA ! REPEAT .
" ASS " AND " BUTT . " YOU LOSE .
[ Tires squealing ]
[ Trish ] I THINK MAYBE SOMETHING 'S WRONG .
[ Darry ] YOU ALWAYS THINK THERE 'S SOMETHING WRONG .
LIKE YOU WOULD NOTICE ANYTHING
PAST THE POINT OF YOUR OWN SELFISH LITTLE EXISTENCE .
SHE 'S NOT HAPPY .
NOT LIKE SHE USED TO BE .
WELL , WHO IS ?
MOM 'S NOT- -
HEY .
IT 'S " BEATING YOU . "
WHAT 'S HE DOING ?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT ?
WHAT THE HELL WAS HE DOING ?
HE DUMPED SOMETHING DOWN THAT PIPE .
WRAPPED IN A SHEET .
WRAPPED AND ROPED IN A SHEET .
WRAPPED AND ROPED IN A SHEET WITH RED STAINS ON IT .
JUST GET US OUT OF HERE .
ALL RIGHT . GRAB MY CELL PHONE .
WHERE ?
IT 'S IN THE GYM BAG .
OH , JESUS ...
OH , YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME .
[ Truck horn blowing ]
THE POINT OF HAVING A PORTABLE PHONE , IDIOT ,
IS THAT IT WORKS WHEN YOU NEED IT !
I HAVE A POWER CABLE FOR IT .
YEAH , AND I HAVE A CIGARETTE LIGHTER THAT DOESN 'T WORK .
AW , GODDAMN IT , WHAT DID I SAY ? MY CAR !
WE SHOULD 'VE TAKEN MY CAR !
HE 'S COMING UP RIGHT ON OUR ASS .
[ Truck horn blowing ]
WHAT THE HELL HAS HE GOT IN THAT THING ?
HE 'S GOT IT SOUPED UP OR SOMETHING .
[ Truck horn blowing ]
DARRY ...
HE 'S COMING UP RIGHT ON OUR ASS .
WHAT THE FUCK IS IN THAT THING ?
AHH !
[ Tires screeching ]
YOU 'RE OUT OF YOUR FUCKING MIND !
[ Engine revving ]
AHH !
WHAT THE HELL 'S YOUR PROBLEM ?
[ Tires screeching ]
FUCK ME !
GEEZ !
GO !
WHAT THE HELL 'S THE MATTER WITH YOU !
[ Truck horn blowing ]
[ Brakes screeching ]
DARRY , WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
HANG ON .
JUST DON 'T KILL US , OK ?
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Birds squawking ]
[ Heavy breathing ]
[ Engine starting ]
SOUNDS ALL RIGHT .
WHAT ?
LIKE EITHER ONE OF US WOULD KNOW .
I KNOW A LITTLE .
YOUR CAR MAKES A STRANGE NOISE ,
YOU JUST GET A NEW TAPE , DARRY . YOU TOLD ME .
I TOLD YOU ?
I LEARNED IT FROM YOU .
JESUS CHRIST ...
[ Darry ] WHOA , WHOA , WHOA , WHOA , WHOA , WAIT , WAIT .
I 'M THINKING PAST THE POINT
OF MY OWN SELFISH LITTLE EXISTENCE NOW , OK ?
WE 'RE BOTH PRETTY DAMN SURE
WHAT WE SAW HIM DUMP DOWN THAT PIPE , RIGHT ?
WHAT IF IT 'S SOMEONE STILL ALIVE ?
WHAT IF IT WAS ?
SOMEONE WHO NEEDS HELP .
WE CAN GET HELP JUST AS FAST BY GETTING TO A PHONE .
YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW FAR WE ARE FROM A PAY PHONE ?
WE WERE JUST ATTACKED , DARRY !
AND YOU DON 'T EVEN WANNA FIND OUT WHY ?
WE LOOK IN THE PIPE , THAT 'S IT .
IS THIS YOUR IDEA OF A LITTLE ADVENTURE OR SOMETHING ?
'CAUSE THIS IS WHY GIRLS ARE SMARTER , OKAY ?
WE LOOK IN THE PIPE ,
IF THERE 'S NOTHING THERE , NOTHING WE CAN DO ,
WE JUST DRIVE ON HOME AND CALL THE COPS .
NOW , YOU KNOW THAT 'S WHAT WE SHOULD DO .
BULLSHIT , I DO .
BULLSHIT , YOU DON 'T !
LOOK ME IN THE EYE AND TELL ME YOU CAN JUST DRIVE AWAY .
JUST DRIVE OFF , LEAVE WHO 'S EVER BACK THERE , BACK THERE .
MAYBE FIND OUT LATER THEY 'D STILL BE ALIVE IF YOU 'D JUST GONE BACK .
DON 'T MAKE THIS ABOUT THE RIGHT THING TO DO .
YOU JUST WANNA GO BACK AND THERE SEE
IF THERE 'S SOMETHING NASTY AT THE END OF THAT PIPE .
[ Sighing ]
OK .
WHAT IF IT WAS YOU BACK THERE ?
I 'M NOT GETTING OUT OF THIS CAR .
YOU DON 'T HAVE TO .
I 'M NOT .
[ Crows cawing ]
[ Darry ] JESUS , IT 'S A CHURCH .
WHAT 'S WITH ALL THE BIRDS ?
I 'M JUST GONNA LOOK .
[ Crows cawing ]
LET 'S DO THIS AND DO IT FAST .
OH , MY GOD .
OHH .
DOESN 'T LOOK LIKE A SEWER PIPE .
YEAH , DOESN 'T SMELL LIKE ONE EITHER .
COME ON , DARRY , YOU CAN 'T SEE ANYTHING IN THERE .
NO , NO , NO , YOU CAN SEE LIGHT DOWN THERE .
GET A FLASHLIGHT .
COME ON , GET A FLASHLIGHT .
HELLO !
ANYBODY DOWN THERE ?
HEY !
HELLO !
HURRY UP . COME ON .
THERE 'S SOMEONE DOWN THERE , I JUST HEARD THEM .
HELLO !
YOU 'RE HEARING THINGS , DARRY .
DARRY , DON 'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT !
DARRY !
I TOLD YOU I HEARD SOMEONE .
OK . YOU KNOW THE PART IN SCARY MOVIES
WHERE SOMEBODY DOES SOMETHING REALLY STUPID
AND EVERYBODY HATES THEM FOR IT ?
THIS IS IT .
[ Voice whimpering ]
HELLO !
NO , DARRY !
LET ME SLIDE DOWN .
GODDAMN IT !
JUST LET ME GET A LITTLE WAY IN .
YOU 'RE NOT GOING DOWN THERE .
I 'M NOT . JUST- -
ALL RIGHT , HOLD MY FEET .
THE FEET ?
[ Sighing ]
ANYBODY DOWN THERE ?
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU WASHED THESE SOCKS ?
I SEE SOMETHING .
[ Darry ] HELLO !
I AM COUNTING TO 10 .
SOMETHING 'S MOVING DOWN THERE .
AND THEN I AM LETTING GO AND GOING BACK TO MY CAR .
QUIET !
I JUST SAW IT AGAIN .
OK . SOMETHING IS DEFINITELY MOVING DOWN THERE .
AHH !
DARRY !
RATS !
[ Trish ] WHAT ?
IT 'S RATS !
RATS !
AHH !
AAH ! AAH !
DARRY !
OH GOD , DARRY , TALK TO ME !
DARRY , SAY SOMETHING !
MM ...
HMM .
ARE YOU OK ?
[ Moaning ]
HOW THE HELL ARE YOU GONNA GET OUT OF THERE , DAR ?
ARGH .
[ Gasping ]
[ Darry ] OH , YOU SUCK .
[ Trish ] OH ...
GOD , I AM SO SORRY .
OH , I BET YOU ARE .
[ Trish ] I AM . I DON 'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED .
YOU WERE KICKING AND I COULDN 'T HOLD ON TO YOU- -
NOT AS SORRY AS I AM .
HEY , THERE WERE RATS COMING AT MY FACE .
THEY WERE RUNNING AT ME TOO , TRISH .
[ Trish ] I FEEL REALLY BAD . ARE YOU OK ?
AH ...
THANK YOU SO MUCH , BY THE WAY . THANK YOU FOR THIS .
TRISHA JENNER , COMING THROUGH IN THE CLUTCH .
THANK YOU .
[ Trish ] HEY , YOU WERE THE ONE WHO WANTED
TO COME BACK HERE AND HAVE A LITTLE ADVENTURE .
OH , SHUT UP .
[ Trisha ] HOW THE HELL ARE YOU GONNA GET OUT OF THERE ?
DARRY ?
WHAT ?
SAY IT ISN 'T SO .
DID I HEAR YOU TALKING ?
[ Trish ] DARRY , WHO IN THE HOLY HELL ARE YOU TALKING TO DOWN THERE ?
I FOUND OUR BODY .
YOU WHAT ?
I FOUND OUR- -
AAH ! JESUS !
DARRY !
AHH , GET OFF !
JESUS !
[ Whimpering ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Inaudible ]
WHAT ?
[ Exhaling ]
[ Trish ] DARRY ?
SAY SOMETHING . YOU 'RE SCARING THE SHIT OUT OF ME !
DARRY , TELL ME WHAT 'S GOING ON !
[ Trish ] WHAT ?
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE .
[ Trish ] NO , LET 'S STAY AND FEED THE BIRDS .
GET HELP .
GET HELP , TRISH .
[ Trish ] WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT ?
GET OUT TO THE ROAD AND FIND SOMEBODY WHO CAN HELP .
WELL , HOW ARE YOU GONNA GET OUT OF THERE ?
THIS IS--THIS IS--THIS IS SOME--SOME KIND OF BASEMENT , RIGHT , FOR THE CHURCH ?
OH , YOU DON 'T THINK I 'M GOING IN THERE , DO YOU ?
GET OUT TO THE ROAD , FLAG DOWN ANYONE YOU SEE ,
TELL THEM TO GET THE COPS OUT HERE RIGHT AWAY .
[ Darry ] THERE 'S GOTTA BE A WAY OUT . I 'M GONNA FIND IT .
AND TRISH ,
IF YOU SEE THAT OLD TRUCK COMING ,
YOU GET BACK TO THIS PIPE ,
YOU HOLLER DOWN AS LOUD AS YOU CAN .
YOU JUST HAD TO SAY THAT , RIGHT ?
[ Crow cawing ]
[ Crows cawing ]
[ Dripping ]
[ Crow cawing ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Sighing ]
[ Crow cawing ]
[ Engine starting ]
[ Gears grinding ]
[ Sighing ]
[ Screaming ]
GODDAMN IT , DARRY !
YOU ASSHOLE !
DARRY ?
DAR ?
[ Trish ] WOULD YOU PLEASE JUST SAY SOMETHING ?
DARRY , YOU 'RE SCARING THE SHIT OUT OF ME !
WE HAVE TO STOP .
DID YOU HEAR ME ?
DARRY ?
SHE DID LOSE HER HEAD .
DARLA LOST HER HEAD ,
JUST LIKE THEY SAID .
AND YOU KNOW WHAT HE DID , TRISH ?
YOU KNOW WHAT HE DID FOR HER ?
HE S-SEWED IT BACK ON .
HE SEWED IT RIGHT BACK ON .
[ Sighing ]
YOU GONNA MAKE A PHONE CALL ?
MM-HMM .
THROW SOME WATER ON YOURSELF .
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU JUST CRAWLED OUT OF A SEWER .
[ Trish ] HE 'S GOING BACK .
HE 'S GOING BACK . COME ON !
COME ON !
EXCUSE ME .
EXCUSE ME , WE NEED HELP .
I-I NEED YOU TO PLEASE CALL THE POLICE .
THE POLICE ?
WE NEED HELP NOW ...
PLEASE !
CAN YOU JUST ... JUST GO TELL THEM WHAT YOU SAW
SO THAT WE CAN GET OUT OF HERE , OK ?
COME ON , BRAT !
I MEAN IT .
I NEED YOU TO HOLD IT TOGETHER .
LOOK AT ME , DARRY .
I 'M SO SCARED , TRISH .
I AM SO SCARED .
HEY , I 'M SCARED , TOO , ALL RIGHT ?
HE 'S GONNA GET BACK TO THAT CHURCH
AND HE 'S GONNA KNOW THAT WE WERE THERE .
[ Telephone rings ]
AHH !
[ Both sighing ]
[ Ring ]
ARE YOU GONNA GET THAT ?
YEAH , HELLO .
[ Woman ] HAVE YOU SEEN THE CATS YET ?
YOU AND YOUR BROTHER .
M-ME AND MY BROTHER ?
YOU AND DARRY . I SAW YOU WITH LOTS OF CATS .
WHO THE HELL IS THIS ? HOW--HOW DO YOU KNOW DARRY ?
WHO IS THIS ?
DARRY ?
HUH ?
YOU KNOW THE CATS I 'M TALKING ABOUT ?
WHO IS THIS ?
YOU HAVE A TORN SHIRT , RIGHT ?
A-AND A BLOODY HAND .
SHIRT 'S TORN JUST ABOVE A SMALL ROSE TATTOO
ON YOUR STOMACH .
WHO IS THIS ?
HOW THE HELL DO YOU KNOW US ?
YOU FOUND ITS HOUSE OF PAIN .
THE WHAT ?
THOSE BODIES DOWN THERE ,
THAT 'S WHAT IT LIKES TO CALL IT ,
ITS HOUSE OF PAIN .
I DON 'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL YOU 'RE TALKING ABOUT .
I DON 'T KNOW IF IT 'S A DEMON OR A DEVIL
OR JUST SOME HUNGRY THING
FROM SOME DARK PLACE IN TIME .
OH , LIKE , I DON 'T KNOW WHAT THE HELL YOU 'RE TALKING ABOUT .
I JUST KNOW IT 'S NOT GONNA STOP COMING AFTER YOU
OR ANYONE ELSE IT WANTS TO ,
'CAUSE , ONCE IT HAS THE SCENT OF SOMETHING IT LIKES ,
IT CAN 'T .
IT CAN 'T STOP .
[ Darry ] IS WHAT ...
[ Trish ] WHAT IS SHE SAYING ?
I SAW THAT AWFUL TRUCK , TOO .
[ Darry ] HUH ?
WITH THE LICENSE PLATE .
" BEATING YOU ? "
THE LICENSE PLATE ON ITS TRUCK .
RIGHT , " BEATING YOU " ?
NO , THINK ABOUT IT .
WHAT ?
THINK ABOUT IT , FOR CHRIST 'S SAKE .
OH , HOLD ON . I NEED YOU TO LISTEN TO THIS .
¶ JEEPERS CREEPERS , WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE PEEPERS ? ¶
¶ JEEPERS CREEPERS , WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE EYES ? ¶
OK .
YOU HEAR THAT SONG , YOU RUN .
AND I MEAN RUN .
'CAUSE THAT SONG MEANS SOMETHING TERRIBLE FOR YOU .
SOMETHING SO TERRIBLE YOU COULDN 'T DREAM OF IT ,
NOT IN YOUR WORST , MOST TERRIBLE NIGHTMARE .
FUCK YOU , LADY !
DARRY .
DARRY ?
HELLO ?
LET 'S TALK WITH THE COPS AND GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE .
[ Crickets chirping ]
¶ [ Country music playing ]
[ Trish ] MAYBE YOU SHOULD 'VE LEFT OUT THE PART ABOUT THAT PHONE CALL .
IT JUST SOUNDS TOO MUCH LIKE A BAD DREAM .
YEAH , WELL , EVERYTHING I SAID I SAW , I SAW .
WHAT , YOU THINK I BUMPED MY HEAD DOWN THERE OR SOMETHING ?
I DIDN 'T SAY THAT .
[ Darry ] THEN YOU BELIEVE ME , RIGHT ?
RIGHT ?
HEY , LOOK ME IN THE EYE AND TELL ME YOU BELIEVE ME .
LOOK ME RIGHT IN THE EYE RIGHT NOW ,
YOU TELL ME YOU BELIEVE EVERYTHING I SAID !
OK , WE 'RE RUNNING THE PLATES
AND WE 'VE GOT SOME PEOPLE ON THEIR WAY OUT TO THE OLD CHURCH .
AND ?
THESE KIDS YOU SAW ON THAT WALL , WHO WERE THEY AGAIN ?
DARLA CLEEWAY AND KENNY ...
BRANDON . BRANDON .
FOUND THEIR CAR ALL SMASHED UP ABOUT 20 YEARS AGO .
AM I REMEMBERING THIS RIGHT ?
YEAH .
[ Trooper ] THOSE BODIES WOULD BE NOTHING BUT BONES BY NOW .
YOU SAID THEY STILL HAD SKIN ON THEM
AND HE HAD A RING ON HIS FINGER .
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING ?
I TOLD YOU , I-I GRABBED ONE OF THEM LIKE THIS .
AND--AND--AND IT WAS HARD , LIKE PETRIFIED WOOD .
LIKE HE PRESERVED THEM OR SOMETHING .
HE 'S GOT THEM ALL STITCHED TOGETHER LIKE SOME KIND OF QUILT .
I 'M JUST TRYING TO GET ALL THE FACTS HERE .
AND I TOLD YOU THE FACTS !
AND THIS GUY DRIVES AN OLD BROWN TRUCK ,
AND IT NEARLY KILLED US .
AND WE SAW HIM THROW A BODY DOWN A PIPE
THAT DUMPS INTO THE CELLAR OF THAT OLD CHURCH .
NOW , THIS GUY MUST HAVE 500 ,
MAYBE 600 BODIES DOWN THERE AND I 'VE SEEN THEM !
HEY , HEY , HEY , HEY , HEY .
STUCK UP ON THE WALLS
LIKE SOME PSYCHO VERSION OF THE SISTINE CHAPEL !
WHAT , WHAT , YOU DON 'T BELIEVE ME ?
DRIVE OUT TO THE OLD CHURCH
IF YOU DON 'T BELIEVE ME , YOU THINK I 'M LYING .
NO ONE 'S SAYING YOU 'RE LYING , DARRY .
GOOD , BECAUSE I 'M NOT LYING !
LOOK AT THIS FROM MY POINT OF VIEW , OK ?
THIS IS A PRETTY BIG STORY YOU 'RE LAYING ON US HERE .
[ Woman ] HEY !
THAT 'S YOUR CAR OUT AT THE PUMPS , ISN 'T IT ?
BUNCH OF FOLKS SAW HIM FROM THE WINDOW .
THE MAN THERE AT YOUR CAR .
HE WAS STANDING THERE AT YOUR CAR ,
S-SNIFFIN ' THAT LAUNDRY ,
HOLDING BIG HANDFULS OF IT UNDER HIS NOSE .
LOOKED LIKE HE WAS LIKING IT , TOO .
WHICH WAY HE RUN OFF , BINKY ?
STILL THINK I BUMPED MY HEAD ?
HUH ?
HE HAD TIME TO GET TO THE CHURCH , THEN BACK HERE .
NOW THIS GUY IS AFTER US !
AND HE 'S AFTER US ' CAUSE HE KNOWS WHAT WE SAW .
AND NOW HE EVEN KNOWS MY NAME .
CENTRAL , THIS IS 037 . COME BACK .
[ Darry ] HEY !
YOU INTERESTED IN A HAND PRINT ?
[ Officer ] 037 , GO AHEAD , PLEASE .
037 , THIS IS CENTRAL .
GO AHEAD .
YOU CAN DUST THAT , RIGHT ? GET A PRINT ?
[ Trooper ] LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY ALREADY DID .
037 , WHAT 'S GOING ON OUT THERE ?
037 , I NEED A RESPONSE , PLEASE .
[ Darry ] THERE IS DEFINITELY SOME WEIRD SHIT GOING ON .
THIS IS CENTRAL . 037 , THAT IS AN AFFIRMATIVE .
[ Darry ] WE SHOULD ALL JUST GET IN THE CAR AND GO . WE SHOULD GO .
WHAT IS YOUR SITUATION ?
037 , PLEASE RESPOND .
HOW 'D HE GET TO THE CHURCH AND BACK TO THE DINER SO FAST ?
WHAT THE HELL WAS HE DOING WITH YOUR CLOTHES ?
HE DRIVES FAST , BUT NOT THAT FAST .
MAYBE HE CAN LEAP TALL BUILDINGS IN A SINGLE BOUND .
HE 'D HAVE TO BE SUPERHUMAN ,
OTHERWISE , THE SMELL WOULD 'VE KILLED HIM .
[ Officer ] PLEASE COME BACK , 037 , OUT THERE ON EAST 9 .
CENTRAL , THIS IS 037 . GO AHEAD .
YEAH , YOU SURE THAT 'S NOT A COUPLE OF LITTLE PYROMANIACS
YOU 'RE ESCORTING OUT THERE ?
GO AHEAD .
THIS OLD CHURCH IS ON FIRE .
I 'M TALKING BURNING OUT OF CONTROL .
I 'M UP TO MY ASS IN FIRE AND RESCUE , BUT I CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW ,
NO ONE 'S GOING INSIDE THIS THING FOR A LONG , LONG TIME .
[ Darry ] INCEST CAPITAL OF THE WORLD .
OH , DON 'T BE SUCH A SNOT .
DON 'T TELL ME YOU ACTUALLY LIKE HIM .
HUH ? WHO ?
OH , PLEASE . WHEN HE WALKED IN
I THOUGHT THE WAITRESS HAD DIALED THE WRONG NUMBER .
THE GUY LOOKED LIKE A STRIP-O-GRAM COP .
[ Laughing ]
LIKE THE MISSING LINK .
I WANNA BRING HIM TO MY ANTHRO CLASS FOR SHOW AND TELL .
IN SPORTS , THE NATIONAL ...
¶ JEEPERS
HOPE YOU KNOW WHICH COWS ...
¶ OHH , BREAK THE SPELL , I JUST ... ¶
[ Skipping radio channels ]
¶ JEEPERS ...
THAT 'S THE SONG ! THAT 'S THE SONG !
WHAT 'S THE MATTER WITH YOU ?
THE WORDS ARE THE SAME . LISTEN .
¶ ... CREEPSHOW , WHERE DID YOU GET THOSE EYES ... ¶
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU ?
THAT 'S THE SONG ! THE SONG SHE WAS PLAYING- - THAT LADY ON THE PHONE !
THESE KIDS SAY THE VEHICLE CHASED THEM DOING OVER 100 , GO AHEAD .
A PRELIMINARY CAME BACK ON THAT DUST
YOU TOOK OFF THE CAR HANDLE .
IT 'S DEAD SKIN .
LONG DEAD , AND THAT 'S WHY IT WAS POWDER .
SAY WHAT ?
[ Banging ]
THAT 'S IT ! THE WORDS ARE THE SAME , LISTEN !
¶ JEEPERS , WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE WEEPERS ¶
[ Banging ]
HOLD ON , CENTRAL , THE SKY IS FALLING .
AHH !
SHE WAS PLAYING THIS SONG TO US , AND SHE SAID IF WE HEARD IT ...
[ Groaning ]
THIS IS IT .
AHH !
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Officer ] 037 , COME IN .
[ Trish ] HEY !
ARE YOU OK IN THERE ?
037 , THIS IS CENTRAL . COME IN .
[ Darry ] TRISH ?
I SAID HELLO !
GET BACK IN THE CAR .
CENTRAL , THIS IS 04 ...
GET BACK IN THE CAR , TRISH !
[ Gasps ]
¶ [ Whistling Jeepers Creepers ]
WHAT IS THAT ?
I 'M NOT SEEING THIS .
[ Slurping ]
WHAT IS HE DOING ?
GO .
OH , GOD .
I 'M TRYING .
GO , GO , GO , GO ! GO , GO , GO , GO .
GO , GO , GO , GO !
[ Gears grinding ]
GO , GO , GO , GO , GO !
I SAID I 'M TRYING !
[ Tires screeching ]
GO !
COME ON , YOU 'RE GONNA KILL US !
I MEAN IT , SLOW DOWN !
SLOW DOWN !
[ Brakes screeching ]
[ Darry ] OH , NO WAY .
THERE 'S A PHONE .
SO ?
SO YOU JUST TOLD ME TO STOP .
I DIDN 'T SAY , " STOP . " I SAID , " SLOW DOWN . "
HOW FAR 'S THE NEXT TOWN ?
YOU MEAN THE NEXT PHONE ?
'CAUSE IT 'S PRETTY GODDAMN FAR .
YOU WANNA WAIT TO FIND OUT ?
[ Darry ] COME ON , TRISH , LOOK AT THIS PLACE .
LET 'S JUST KEEP GOING .
I MEAN IT , COME ON .
YOU DON 'T WANNA GET HELP ?
HELP FROM WHO ?
WE 'LL JUST USE THE PHONE , OK ?
AND CALL WHO ?
I DON 'T KNOW .
AND TELL THEM WHAT ?
" HEY , BUM-FUCK POLICE , I 'M BEING CHASED BY A GUY
" WHO LIKES TO PULL TONGUES OUT OF SEVERED HEADS WITH HIS TEETH .
" IS THERE A SPECIAL EXTENSION FOR THAT ? "
COME ON .
[ Trish ] CHRIST , DO YOU THINK THEY EVEN HAVE A PHONE ?
I 'M GUESSING NO PHONE AND A LOT OF GUNS .
[ Woman ] WHO ARE YOU ?
I SAID , " WHO ARE YOU ? "
I 'M ... PATRICIA JENNER .
THIS IS MY BROTHER DARRY .
[ Woman ] WHAT DO YOU WANT ?
A TELEPHONE ?
I DON 'T HAVE ONE .
I SAY WE KEEP DRIVING TILL WE SEE PEOPLE .
WHAT DO YOU THINK SHE IS ?
[ Sighing ]
WHAT YOU NEED A PHONE FOR IF I HAD ONE ?
I NEED TO CALL THE PERTWILLA COUNTY POLICE .
PERTWILLA ?
THAT 'S THE COUNTY ONE COUNTY BACK .
YOU 'RE IN POHO COUNTY .
THEN POHO POLICE .
BUT I NEED TO CALL SOMEONE .
DON 'T EVEN THINK ABOUT BRINGING THE COPS OUT HERE
WITH THEIR ZONING CRAP .
THEY TRY TO TELL ME HOW MANY CATS
PEOPLE CAN HAVE .
HEH , I 'LL HAVE AS MANY CATS
AS I WANNA HAVE .
YOU CAN TELL THEM THAT FOR ME .
PLEASE , SOMEONE 'S BEEN KILLED .
KILLED , YOU SAY ?
YEAH , A POLICEMAN .
[ Cat meowing ]
HOLY JESUS , I THOUGHT ...
I THOUGHT YOU MEANT ONE OF MY BABIES .
[ Meowing ]
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I JUST SAID ?
LET 'S GET OUT OF HERE .
YOU CAN CALL THE SHERIFF 'S STATION ,
JUST DON 'T GIVE THEM THIS ADDRESS , AND ...
AND TELL THEM TO GO OUT ON THE INTERSTATE
WHERE THEY OUGHT TO BE .
MY BABIES DON 'T LIKE STRANGERS .
HOW ...
HOW MANY BABIES DO YOU HAVE ?
MORE THAN A COUPLE .
WE 'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW .
[ Coyotes howling ]
TELL ME THIS HAPPENS ALL THE TIME .
[ Many cats meowing ]
HOLY SHIT .
[ Cat screeching ]
[ Creaking ]
YOU KIDS GOT ANYONE ELSE WITH YOU ?
WHAT ?
THAT 'S NOT MY SCARECROW .
[ Door opening ]
[ Cocks gun ]
YOU GOT 10 SECONDS
TO GET YOUR ASS OUT OF MY YARD !
AND DON 'T THINK I 'M GONNA TELL YOU TWICE .
GET THE HELL AWAY FROM HIM .
WHAT ARE YOU DOING , TRISH ?
GET THE HELL AWAY FROM HIM !
[ Glass breaking ]
[ Cat screeching ]
COME ON . LET 'S GO .
NO , NO , NO , NO .
DON 'T YOU GO UP THERE .
LISTEN TO HIM !
WE 'VE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE NOW !
WHAT THE HELL DID YOU BRING INTO MY HOUSE ?
AH-AH .
OH , GET OUT OF HERE .
GET AWAY FROM MY BABIES , YOU SONS OF BITCHES !
[ Cats screeching ]
I 'LL BLOW YOUR FUCKING HEAD OFF !
[ Gunshot ]
HELLO ?
[ Woman ] AH ...
[ Croaking ]
AH .
AH-AH-AH .
[ Growling ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Car starting ]
[ Tires squealing ]
[ Gears grinding ]
[ Trish ] SOMETHING 'S WRONG .
DON 'T SAY THAT !
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY ? THE GEARS ARE STICKING !
UNSTICK THEM , TRISH !
YOU 'RE GONNA BREAK IT !
AHH !
GO !
IT 'S STUCK IN REVERSE !
GO IN REVERSE !
[ Brakes squealing ]
[ Whispering ] WHAT DO WE DO ?
HIT HIM .
HIT HIM , TRISH .
HARD .
DO IT !
[ Engine revving ]
[ Brakes squealing ]
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT THING ?
[ Gears grinding ]
[ Darry ] WHAT ARE YOU DOING ? WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING ?
COME ON , YOU SON OF A BITCH .
THAT 'S RIGHT ,
WALK THAT UGLY FACE RIGHT OVER HERE .
COME ON .
COME ON !
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Glass breaks ]
[ Brakes squealing ]
DO YOU THINK HE 'S DEAD ?
THEY NEVER ARE .
[ Engine revving ]
[ Gear grinds ]
[ Brakes squealing ]
[ Tires screeching ]
ENOUGH .
[ Flapping ]
LET 'S GET OUT OF HERE .
TRISH .
TRISH !
[ Gears grinding ]
I DON 'T KNOW HOW MUCH FURTHER THIS CAR 'S GONNA GO .
NOT FAR ENOUGH .
[ Tires screeching ]
[ Incoherent police radios ]
ROACH .
WHAT ARE WE BOOSTING TONIGHT ?
WELL , WHY DON 'T YOU COME OVER HERE AND FIND OUT , BIG DADDY ?
'76 CHEVY NOVA , HUH ?
ANYONE EVER TELL YOU , FOR A CAR THIEF , YOU GOT TASTE FOR SHIT ?
[ Trish ] WOULD YOU TELL DAD TO STOP SHOUTING , PLEASE ?
MOM !
I-I UNDERSTAND THAT , MOTHER .
I 'M JUST TRYING TO TELL YOU WHERE WE ARE .
STANDING RIGHT HERE .
I TOLD YOU , WE 'RE BOTH OK .
IT 'S THE POHO COUNTY SHERIFF 'S STATION
ABOUT 20 MILES OUTSIDE PERTWILLA .
BECAUSE WE 'LL BE HOME BEFORE YOU COULD GET HERE .
WE DON 'T WANNA WAIT HERE , MOM .
WE JUST WANNA GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE .
MOM , JUST ... LET US GET HOME , OK ?
WE DON 'T WANNA BE OUT HERE ANY MORE THAN YOU DO .
ME , TOO .
I 'LL TALK TO YOU IN A FEW HOURS .
DAD .
THOUGHT I WRECKED THE CAR ?
MM-HMM .
[ Darry ] SHE 'S TRAILER TRASH .
[ Trish ] PIG FUCKER .
BOOGER EATER .
TRISHA ?
TRISHA AND DARRY , RIGHT ?
JEZ , WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
EXCUSE ME ...
JEZELLE ?
DARRY .
DARRY JENNER .
JEZELLE GAY HARTMAN . HOW DO YOU DO ?
JEZ , COME ON . THEY 'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT , OKAY ?
TRISHA . GODDAMN IT , JEZ .
I REALLY NEED TO TALK TO YOU ,
IF YOU COULD JUST SPARE ME A MINUTE .
JEZELLE LIKES TO THINK SHE 'S THE RESIDENT PSYCHIC AROUND HERE .
SHE HELPED US WITH A MISSING PERSONS- -
DO YOU THINK COULD I JUST TALK TO THESE KIDS BY MYSELF ?
YOU GO HOME ,
TURN OFF THAT POLICE SCANNER , AND GO TO BED .
YOU GOT MISSING PERSONS AND A FIRE IN THE NEXT COUNTY .
GO DO SOMETHING USEFUL .
[ Telephone ringing ]
JEZELLE , I MEAN IT , NOW , LEAVE THEM ALONE .
YOU DON 'T HAVE TO BELIEVE I 'M PSYCHIC .
YOU DON 'T HAVE TO BELIEVE A WORD I SAY .
BUT I 'VE COME A VERY LONG WAY TO SEE YOU .
YOU KNOW ,
I 'M NOT REALLY SURE WE SHOULD BE TALKING TO ANYBODY RIGHT NOW .
LET ' S GO .
YOU FOUND ALL THOSE BODIES
DOWN IN THAT CELLAR .
I SAW THEM , TOO .
HOW ?
DREAMED IT .
I DREAM A LOT OF THINGS .
YOU SEE THE CATS YET ?
I SAW YOU WITH ALL THOSE CATS , TOO .
THE DINER .
THAT WAS YOU . YOU CALLED US .
WILL YOU EXCUSE ME FOR A SECOND ?
DARRY , I NEED TO TALK- -
I NEED YOU TO LISTEN AND NOT TALK , OK ?
TRUTH BE , I 'D BE LYING IF I SAID
I KNEW THAT TELLING YOU THIS WOULD DO ANY GOOD .
ANY GOOD ?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN ?
EVERY 23RD SPRING ,
FOR 23 DAYS ,
IT GETS TO ...
EAT .
EAT ?
YOU KNOW WHAT IT EATS , AND DON 'T YOU MAKE ME TELL YOU .
YOU THINK I LIKE HAVING THIS IN MY HEAD ?
WELL , I DON 'T .
I DON 'T LIKE KNOWING THIS AND NOT KNOWING WHY I DO .
YOU SAID IT EATS ?
ONLY ...
CERTAIN THINGS ...
FROM CERTAIN PEOPLE .
JUST GET AWAY FROM HER , DARRY .
IT EATS LUNGS ...
SO IT CAN BREATHE ,
AND EYES ...
SO IT CAN SEE .
IT ALL BECOMES A PART OF IT .
WHATEVER IT EATS ... BECOMES A PART OF IT .
IT DRESSES LIKE A MAN ,
BUT ONLY TO HIDE THAT IT 'S NOT .
[ Engine stopping ]
YOU HURT IT ...
OUT THERE ON THE ROAD
[ Door opening ]
BUT ONLY AS MUCH AS IT CAN BE HURT .
'CAUSE IT CAN KEEP ON EATING
TILL IT ISN 'T HURT NO MORE .
[ Gushy footsteps ]
YOU 'VE GOT SOMETHING IT LIKES ,
ONE OF YOU .
AND IT 'S NOT GONNA STOP CHASING YOU
TILL IT KNOWS WHICH ONE .
HOW ?
NEVER MIND HOW .
NO , HOW DOES IT FIND OUT , BY RUNNING PEOPLE OFF THE ROAD ?
IT NEEDS TO SCARE YOU .
THERE 'S SOMETHING IN FEAR , SOMETHING IT CAN SMELL .
SOMETHING THAT TELLS IT IF THERE 'S
ANYTHING INSIDE SOMEONE THAT IT MIGHT ...
LIKE .
YOU 'RE TELLING US THIS THING IS OUT DRIVING DOWN THE HIGHWAY ,
TRYING TO FREAK PEOPLE OUT SO IT CAN SMELL THEM ?
CHRIST , DARRY ! WHY ARE WE STANDING HERE WITH HER ?
[ Men 's voices ] HEY , HEY ! HO , HO , HO !
HELLO ?
WE GOT LIGHTS AND PHONES OUT UP HERE !
WOULD SOMEBODY TALK TO ME ?
IT 'S GONE .
WE RAN IT OVER TILL THERE WAS NOTHING LEFT .
WHAT THE HELL , HAVE WE GOT EMERGENCY LIGHTS OR WHAT ?
[ Sergeant ] ALL RIGHT , PEOPLE , WE 'RE GOING INTO A LOCKDOWN SITUATION .
THAT MEANS EVERYBODY SIT TIGHT ,
DON 'T MOVE UNLESS SOMEBODY WEARING A BADGE TELLS YOU .
WE POUNDED IT TO DUST .
WATCHED IT BLOW THE FUCK AWAY .
I THINK IT 'S EATEN TOO MANY HEARTS
FOR ITS OWN TO EVER STOP .
[ Cellblock officer ] HEADS UP , GENTLEMEN .
HEADS UP .
LET ME SEE SOME SKIN .
ARE YOU IN A COMA , BUDDY ?
WHAT THE HELL 'S WRONG WITH YOU , MAN ?
[ Officer ] WE HAVE A BLACKOUT . THAT MEANS EMERGENCY HEAD COUNT .
HEY , LOWER BUNK , LET ME SEE SOME SKIN .
THAT IS SPECIAL . I LOVE YOU , TOO .
HEADS UP . HEADS UP ,
MOVE IT , DOWN THERE .
THANK YOU . THANK YOU FOR JOINING US .
SHOW ME SOME SKIN , THAT 'S IT .
HEADS UP , GENTLEMEN .
GENTLEMEN- -
[ Growling ]
[ Slurping ]
[ Rattling ]
[ Tearing ]
[ Chewing and swallowing ]
[ Cocks gun ]
[ Gunshot ]
AAH !
OKAY , YOU 2 . YOU KIDS WANNA COME WITH ME ?
WE 'RE PUTTING YOU IN A HOLDING ROOM .
YOU CAN 'T DO THAT ! HE FINDS YOU IN HERE !
HE FINDS YOU HIDING IN A ROOM !
YOU , TOO .
¶ JEEPERS CREEPERS
¶ WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE PEEPERS ? ¶
WE HEARD IT IN THE CAR HOURS AGO .
NO . IT 'S PLAYING ON AN OLD PHONOGRAPH .
ESCORT JEZELLE HERE TO THE BIG BLUE WINNEBAGO ,
SHE 'S NO DOUBT BLOCKING THE DRIVEWAY WITH .
¶ JEEPERS CREEPERS , WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE EYES ? ¶
[ Sergeant ] I SWEAR I WILL LOCK YOU UP , JEZ .
I HEAR IT PLAYING WHILE ONE OF YOU IS SCREAMING .
SCREAMING DOWN IN THE DARK SOMEWHERE .
SCREAMING THE LAST SCREAM YOU 'LL EVER SCREAM !
ALL RIGHT NOW , GODDAMN IT , KNOCK IT OFF !
WHAT EXACTLY ARE YOU DOING HERE ?
[ Officer ] UP TOP ? ANYBODY ON GROUND LEVEL ? WE HAVE AN 11-99 .
I REPEAT , AN 11-99 .
THIS IS TUBBS , GO AHEAD .
WE GOT A SITUATION DOWN HERE , SARGE .
IT 'S HEADED TOWARDS YOU , UP THE REAR STAIRS . YOU COPY ?
COMING UP THE REAR STAIRWELL .
STAY HERE .
[ Alarm ringing ]
I 'M GONNA GET YOU OUT OF HERE .
COME ON , I SAID !
[ Shouting ]
[ Tubbs ] SOMEBODY DOWN THERE TALK TO ME .
[ Officer ] WE HAVE ONE INMATE AND ONE OFFICER DOWN .
RAMIREZ , HE 'S HURT BAD .
THE SON OF A BITCH , HE TRIED TO TAKE A BITE OUT OF HIM .
HE WHAT ?
[ Banging ]
THIS GUY IS WEARING SOMETHING , SARGE .
'CAUSE I 'M A SON OF A BITCH , BUT WE CANNOT TAKE HIM DOWN .
WHAT THE HELL DO YOU MEAN , " WEARING SOMETHING " ?
YOU 'D THINK I WAS CRAZY IF I TOLD YOU .
THIS IS ABOUT THE WEIRDEST FUCKING BODY ARMOR YOU 'VE EVER SEEN .
[ Banging ]
WHERE ... WHERE IS HE ?
TALK .
HE 'S GONE .
HE 'S GONE , SARGE .
THIS GUY JUST CLIMBED UP THE FUCKING WALL .
YOU ARE NOT MAKING ONE GODDAMN BIT OF SENSE .
YOU CAN PUT ME IN A STRAITJACKET , SARGE , BUT THIS FUCKER IS GONE .
GONE ? WHAT THE HELL YOU TALKING ABOUT , GONE ?
THIS GUY 'S A REAL MOVER AND A SHAKER , SARGE .
WE JUST LOST HIM ON THE STAIRWELL .
[ Officer # 2 ] I CAN 'T SEE ! I CAN 'T SEE !
[ Officer # 1 ] HE 'S HEADING RIGHT UP TO YOU . COPY ?
AHH !
[ Shouting ]
SHIT .
THIS IS YOUR WAY OUT ?
THESE MUST LOCK AUTOMATICALLY IF THE POWER 'S OUT .
YOU DIDN 'T KNOW THAT ?
I DON 'T DREAM EVERYTHING !
THIS ISN 'T EVERYTHING ! THIS IS OUR WAY OUT !
IT 'S NOT LIKE WATCHING A MOVIE , HONEY .
THERE ARE PARTS MISSING SOMETIMES .
[ Trish whispers ] WE HAVE TO GET OUT OF HERE NOW .
THERE 'S NO OTHER WAY EXCEPT THE FRONT ...
WELL , THE FRONT DOOR IS OUT !
WHY DON 'T YOU DREAM UP SOMETHING USEFUL ?
I THOUGHT IF YOU KNEW WHAT I SAW , MAYBE YOU COULD CHANGE IT .
WHY THE HELL DO YOU THINK I 'M HERE ?
YOU KNOW .
DON 'T YOU ?
YOU KNEW WHEN YOU WALKED IN .
YOU KNOW WHO IT WANTS .
YOU KNOW WHAT IT WANTS .
[ Jezelle ] I 'VE DREAMED THIS .
YOU KNOW WHAT 'S GONNA HAPPEN .
YOU WILL RUN UP THE STAIRS AND HIDE ,
BUT I DON 'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENS TO ME .
JEEPERS CREEPERS .
JEEPERS CREEPERS , RIGHT ?
WHO ?
WHO HEARS JEEPERS CREEPERS
WHILE SCREAMING IN THE DARK ?
HUH ?
ARE THEY EVER WRONG ?
I DON 'T BELIEVE YOU .
YOU DON 'T UNDERSTAND .
YOUR DREAMS , ARE THEY EVER WRONG ?
YOU GO TO HELL .
I SAID , YOU DON 'T UNDERSTAND .
ARE THEY EVER WRONG ? ARE YOUR DREAMS EVER WRONG ?
[ Trish ] SHE DOESN 'T KNOW .
SHE DOESN 'T KNOW SHIT .
GET UPSTAIRS !
NOW !
OUR FATHER , WHO ART IN HEAVEN ,
HALLOWED BE THY ...
UH ?
AHH !
[ Growling ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Both ] AHH !
AH-AH , AH-AH , OH-OH ... .
[ Growling ]
AAH .
[ High-pitched shrieking ]
WHAT ... IN THE HOLY NAME OF GOD ?
OH ...
I CAN 'T , I CAN 'T ...
TAKE ME .
YOU DON 'T WANT HIM .
WHATEVER YOU WANT ,
YOU CAN TAKE IT FROM ME .
YOU DON 'T WANT DARRY .
NO , YOU DON 'T .
DON 'T YOU- -
DON 'T YOU BE A HERO !
I HAVE EVERYTHING THE SAME INSIDE . YOU TAKE ME !
[ Darry ] IT 'S OK .
YOU HEAR ME ? YOU TAKE ME .
YOU FUCKING LET HIM GO !
[ Growling ]
PLEASE ... PLEASE , LET HIM GO .
TRISH ,
PLEASE DON 'T DO THIS .
JUST THINK FOR A SECOND .
I WON 'T FIGHT YOU . YOU CAN TAKE ME .
I 'M STRONGER . YOU WANT ME .
DROP HIM .
LET HIM GO AND TAKE ME .
YOU LET HIM GO !
[ Trish ] DARRY !
DARRY !
YOUR FOLKS JUST PULLED UP OUTSIDE .
YOU NEVER ANSWERED HIM .
ARE YOUR DREAMS EVER WRONG ?
DARRY SCREAMING IN THE DARK
WHILE THAT SONG IS PLAYING .
WHAT DID THAT MEAN ?
WHAT DID YOU REALLY SEE ?
I 'M JUST A CRAZY OLD WOMAN .
YOU ASK ANYONE AROUND HERE , THEY 'LL TELL YOU .
THAT 'S ALL I AM .
JUST A CRAZY OLD WOMAN
WITH CRAZY DREAMS .
[ Crow cawing ]
[ Darry screaming ]
[ Darry screaming and crying ]
¶ [ Jeepers Creepers playing on phonograph ]
¶ WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE EYES
¶ GOLLY JEE WHEN YOU TURN THOSE HEATERS ON ¶
¶ WOE IS ME GOT TO PUT MY CHEATERS ON ¶
¶ JEEPERS CREEPERS WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE PEEPERS ¶
¶ OH , THOSE WEEPERS
¶ HOW THEY HYPNOTIZE
¶ KNOCK ME OUT
¶ WHERE 'D YOU GET THOSE EYES
¶ WHERE 'D YOU GET ' EM
¶ WON 'T YOU PUT ME WISE
¶ PAYS TO ADVERTISE
¶ TELL ' EM ' BOUT THEM
¶ WHERE DID YOU GET THOSE EYES ¶
¶ [ HUSH , HUSH , HERE COMES THE BOGEY MAN playing ]
¶ CHILDREN HAVE YOU EVER MET THE BOGEY MAN BEFORE ¶
¶ NO , OF COURSE YOU HAVEN 'T
¶ FOR YOU 'RE MUCH TOO GOOD , I 'M SURE ¶
¶ DON 'T YOU BE AFRAID OF HIM IF HE SHOULD VISIT YOU ¶
¶ HE 'S A GREAT BIG COWARD SO I 'LL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO ¶
¶ HUSH , HUSH , HUSH
¶ HERE COMES THE BOGEY MAN
¶ DON 'T LET HIM COME TOO CLOSE TO YOU ¶
¶ HE 'LL CATCH YOU IF HE CAN
¶ JUST PRETEND THAT YOU 'RE A CROCODILE ¶
¶ AND YOU WILL FIND THAT BOGEY MAN WILL RUN AWAY A MILE ¶
¶ SAY " SHOO-SHOO " AND STICK HIM WITH A PIN ¶
¶ BOGEY MAN WILL VERY NEARLY JUMP OUT OF HIS SKIN ¶
¶ SAY " BUGS-BUGS " JUST LIKE THE WASP THAT STINGS ¶
¶ BOGEY MAN WILL THINK YOU ARE AN ELEPHANT WITH WINGS ¶
¶ HUSH , HUSH , HUSH
¶ HERE COMES THE BOGEY MAN
¶ TELL HIM YOU GOT SOLDIERS IN YOUR BED ¶
¶ FOR HE WILL NEVER GUESS THAT THEY ARE ONLY MADE OF LEAD ¶
¶ SAY " HUSH-HUSH " HE 'LL THINK THAT YOU 'RE ASLEEP ¶
¶ IF YOU MAKE A LOVELY SNORE AWAY HE 'LL SOFTLY CREEP ¶
¶ SING THIS TUNE YOU CHILDREN ONE AND ALL ¶
¶ BOGEY MAN WILL RUN AWAY HE 'LL THINK IT 'S HENRY HALL ¶
¶ WHEN THE SHADOWS OF THE EVENING PEEP ACROSS THE SKY ¶
¶ AND YOUR MUMMY COMES UPSTAIRS TO SING A LULLABY ¶
¶ TELL HER THAT THE BOGEY MAN NO LONGER FRIGHTENS YOU ¶
¶ UNCLE HENRY 'S VERY KINDLY TOLD YOU WHAT TO DO ¶
¶ HUSH , HUSH , HUSH HERE COMES THE BOGEY MAN ¶
¶ DON 'T LET HIM COME TOO CLOSE TO YOU ¶
¶ HE 'LL CATCH YOU IF HE CAN
¶ JUST PRETEND YOUR TEDDY BEAR 'S A DOG ¶
¶ THEN SHOUT OUT , " FETCH HIM TEDDY " ¶
¶ AND HE 'LL HOP OFF LIKE A FROG ¶
¶ SAY " MEOW " , PRETEND THAT YOU 'RE A CAT ¶
¶ HE 'LL THINK YOU MAY SCRATCH HIM ¶
¶ THAT WILL MAKE HIM FALL DOWN FLAT ¶
¶ JUST PRETEND HE ISN 'T REALLY THERE ¶
¶ YOU WILL FIND THAT BOGEY MAN WILL VANISH IN THIN AIR ¶
¶ HERE 'S ONE WAY TO CATCH HIM WITHOUT FAIL ¶
¶ JUST KEEP A LITTLE SALT WITH YOU ¶
¶ AND PUT IT ON HIS TAIL